[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which part of the digestive system are the so-called Brunners glands located?", "correct_answer": "Duodenum", "incorrect_answers": ["Stomach", "Colon", "Small intestine"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "These knee-breeches made of leather are a traditional Bavarian garment.", "correct_answer": "Lederhosen", "incorrect_answers": ["Kilt", "Kisen", "Wrestlers"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Papillon is a small dog breed of the Toy group. What does the word Papillon mean in French?", "correct_answer": "Butterfly", "incorrect_answers": ["Cherry", "Flower", "Angel"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the real name of the woman in the movie Chinatown who approached Jake claiming to be Evelyn Cross Mulwray?", "correct_answer": "Ida Sessions", "incorrect_answers": ["Ingrid Sample", "Penelope Cramdon", "Lana Lutts"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who said We\u2019re gonna get us some farm girls.?", "correct_answer": "George Kennedy in Cool Hand Luke", "incorrect_answers": ["Kevin Bacon in Footloose", "Burt Reynolds in Semi-Tough", "Gene Hackman in Bonnie and Clyde"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who built the famous monument Taj Mahal?", "correct_answer": "Shah Jehan", "incorrect_answers": ["Akbar", "Aurangzeb", "Babur"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these movie characters based on real people was not portrayed by Robert De Niro?", "correct_answer": "Don Michael Corleone", "incorrect_answers": ["Vito Corleone", "Jimmy Conway", "Jake LaMotta"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What business did the Wright brothers, Orville and Wilbur, operate before beginning their aeronautical work?", "correct_answer": "cycle company", "incorrect_answers": ["film company", "car company", "book store"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Despite its natural origins, this food is particularly bad for your teeth; it is sticky and contains concentrated fruit sugar.", "correct_answer": "Dried fruits", "incorrect_answers": ["Puree", "Chocolate Milk", "Juice"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The tagline for the movie A Fistful of Dollars was: For Three Men The Civil War Wasnt Hell. It Was Practice!", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which Grammy Award-nominated actor and rapper played Anthony in the 2004 movie Crash?", "correct_answer": "Ludacris", "incorrect_answers": ["Will Smith", "Jay-Z", "LL Cool J"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Three of the listed singers are baritones. Who is the odd one?", "correct_answer": "Roberto Alagna", "incorrect_answers": ["Elvis Presley", "Robert Goulet", "Frank Sinatra"]}]